Guide to the Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography MSS.498
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX. Films, 1981-2007, undated; 6 Linear Feet in 6 record cartons.; 173 videocassettes (vhs); 120 videodiscs (dvd)
  - Subseries IX.A. Videocassettes (VHS), 1981-2004, undated; 4 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons.; 173 videocassettes (vhs)
    - Hot Cops #2, California, Palm Drive Video, 1996; cuid25046 (Box 28)
    - Hot Jobs, Undated; cuid25047 (Box 28)
    - Industrial Strength, Cove Lane Productions, Undated; cuid25048 (Box 28)
    - Industrial Strength, Pig Boy Leather, Undated; cuid25049 (Box 28)
    - Joy Riders, T&T Productions, Undated; cuid25050 (Box 28)
    - Jungle Heat, Kristen Bjorn, Florida, Kristen Bjorn Productions, 1993; cuid25051 (Box 28)
    - Kansas City Trucking Co., Joe Gage, California, HIS Video, 1990; cuid25052 (Box 28)
    - L.A.P.D., Undated; cuid25053 (Box 28)
    - La Tool & Die, Joe Gage, California, HIS Video, 1990; cuid25054 (Box 28)
    - Leather Obsession, California, Palm Drive Video, 1994; cuid25055 (Box 28)
    - Leather Obsession IV: Forever, California, Palm Drive Video, 1995; cuid25056 (Box 28)
    - Ledermeister, Colt Studio, 1987; cuid25057 (Box 28)
    - Magnum Griffin Vol. II, Undated; cuid25058 (Box 29)
    - Man Eating Man, Undated; cuid25059 (Box 29)
    - Manifesto, California, Palm Drive Video, Undated; cuid25060 (Box 29)
    - Marine Furlough, Undated; cuid25061 (Box 29)
    - Martin of Holland, Undated; cuid25062 (Box 29)
    - The Meat Locker, Frank Ross, Live Video, Undated; cuid25063 (Box 29)
    - Muscle Ranch!, Buckshot Productions, 1991; cuid25064 (Box 29)
    - My Masters, Christopher Rage, Undated; cuid25065 (Box 29)
    - Mystery Men, Kristen Bjorn, 1994; cuid25066 (Box 29)
    - N.Y.P.D., Undated; cuid25067 (Box 29)
    - Oil Patch (Sampler - plus freebie), Undated; cuid25068 (Box 29)
    - Orgy, HIS Video, 1983; cuid25069 (Box 29)
    - Outrage, Christopher Rage, His Video, 1985; cuid25070 (Box 29)
    - Party Animal, California, Palm Drive Video, 1998; cuid25071 (Box 29)
    - Pig Pen, Frank Ross, Undated; cuid25072 (Box 29)
    - Pig Sty, Frank Ross, Undated; cuid25073 (Box 29)
    - Pig Sty, Undated; cuid25074 (Box 29)
    - Pigs at the Hole, Undated; cuid25075 (Box 29)
    - Piss Drinkers and Bareback Fuckers, SX Video, Undated; cuid25076 (Box 29)
    - Piss Off, Undated; cuid25077 (Box 29)
    - Piss Police, Undated; cuid25078 (Box 29)
    - Piss Slaves, Undated; cuid25079 (Box 29)
    - Piss, Piss and More Piss, California, SX Video, Undated; cuid25080 (Box 29)
    - Pits, Tits and Feet, Bob Jones Productions, Undated; cuid25081 (Box 29)
    - Plantin' Seed, Paul Morris, California, Treasure Island Media, 2004; cuid25082 (Box 29)
    - Playing Fire, 1995; cuid25083 (Box 29)
    - Power Pissing, Undated; cuid25084 (Box 29)
    - Powerhouse Bears, California, Palm Drive Video, Undated; cuid25085 (Box 29)
    - Preview Tape #1, T&T Productions, 1998; cuid25086 (Box 29)
    - Rage Custom #8 - vol. 2, Christopher Rage, 1988; cuid25087 (Box 29)
    - Raunch, Christopher Rage, 1983; cuid25088 (Box 29)
    - Raunch Lunch, Undated; cuid25089 (Box 29)
    - Raunch Lunch, Paul Morris, Treasure Island Media, 1998; cuid25090 (Box 29)
    - Raunch Two, Christopher Rage, 1985; cuid25091 (Box 29)
    - Read Bi All, California, All Worlds Video, 1998; cuid25092 (Box 29)
    - The Rex Video Gallery, California, Palm Drive Video, Undated; cuid25093 (Box 29)
    - Rim Shots, Jack Stone, Live Video, Undated; cuid25094 (Box 29)
    - Rim-Crazy Buttsucker, Tom Gloryhole, California, Palm Drive Video, Undated; cuid25095 (Box 29)
    - Rimmers and more Rimmers, Undated; cuid25096 (Box 29)
    - Rimming Slaves, Bob Jones Productions, Undated; cuid25097 (Box 29)
    - Rob Lowe Sex Tape; Backstage with the Go-Gos; Chuck Berry Sex Tape, Midnight Blue, Undated; cuid25098 (Box 29)
    - Rockland, Undated; cuid25099 (Box 29)
    - Rusco's Revenge, Bob Jones Productions, Undated; cuid25100 (Box 29)
    - Russo, You CumWhore!, Undated; cuid25101 (Box 29)
    - Sailor in the Wild, California, Laguna Pacific LTd, 1984; cuid25102 (Box 30)
    - Sailor in the Wind, California, Laguna Pacific, 1985; cuid25103 (Box 30)
    - Screen Play, Trophy Video, Undated; cuid25104 (Box 30)
    - Second Party Tape, Christoper Rage, 1990; cuid25105 (Box 30)
    - Sex Drive, Jean-Daniel Cadinot, Marksman Production, Undated; cuid25106 (Box 30)
    - Sex Pigs, New York, 3rd World Video, 1998; cuid25107 (Box 30)
    - Sgt. O'Brein's Secret, Undated; cuid25108 (Box 30)
    - Shadows in the Night, Falcon, 1992; cuid25109 (Box 30)
    - The Shaft, Christoper Rage, 1987; cuid25110 (Box 30)
    - Shaved, Hosed & Barebacked, Undated; cuid25111 (Box 30)
    - Slave Workshop L.A., Undated; cuid25112 (Box 30)
    - Slobber, Frank Ross, Undated; cuid25113 (Box 30)
    - Slobber, Frank Ross, Undated; cuid25114 (Box 30)
    - Sludgemaster I, Undated; cuid25115 (Box 30)
    - Sludgemaster II, Undated; cuid25116 (Box 30)
      Duration: 108 minutes
    - Sperminator 2, Jack Cummings, Undated; cuid25117 (Box 30)
    - Stop! In the Name of Sex, Undated; cuid25118 (Box 30)
    - Straight Pick Up, Bob Jones Productions, Undated; cuid25119 (Box 30)
    - Superstars, Christoper Rage, California, VCA Labs, 1990; cuid25120 (Box 30)
    - Swallow...More, Paul Morris, California, Treasure Island Media, 2001; cuid25121 (Box 30)
    - Taboo: Raw Studs, Justin Thomas, Florida, 2002; cuid25122 (Box 30)
    - Taking It All, Undated; cuid25123 (Box 30)
    - Taste of Leather 2, Catalina, 1994; cuid25124 (Box 30)
    - A Taste of Torture, California, Shotgun, 2001; cuid25125 (Box 30)
    - Tom Cum Crazy Cocksucker, California, Palm Drive Video, Undated; cuid25126 (Box 30)
    - Tom Gloryholes #5: Big Wiener Picnic, California, Palm Drive Video, 1995; cuid25127 (Box 30)
    - Tongue Dancing, Undated; cuid25128 (Box 30)
    - Tongue Devils, Undated; cuid25129 (Box 30)
    - Tough Competition, California, Hot Videos, 1984; cuid25130 (Box 30)
    - Towel Off! Back to the Baths part 2, California, Marco Studio, 1999; cuid25131 (Box 30)
    - Tramps, Chris Rage, Live Video, Undated; cuid25132 (Box 30)
    - Trash, Jack Stone, Live Video, 1993; cuid25133 (Box 30)
    - Turned On, Undated; cuid25134 (Box 30)
    - Valentine's Day / Beautiful Extremes / Men live this way / Life is all it seems, Undated; cuid25135 (Box 30)
    - Very Yellow with Stains of Brown, Undated; cuid25136 (Box 30)
    - Wet, Undated; cuid25137 (Box 30)
    - Wet and Wild, Glory Hole Studs, 2002; cuid25138 (Box 30)
    - Wetter, Jack Stone, Live Video, 1993; cuid25139 (Box 30)
    - What Hollywood Pissed Away, Undated; cuid25140 (Box 30)
    - What Pigs Do Best, Donnie Russo, Undated; cuid25141 (Box 30)
    - Wildside, HIS Video, 1984; cuid25142 (Box 30)
  - Subseries IX.B. Videodiscs (DVDs), 1995-2007, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons.; 120 videodiscs (dvd)
    The DVDs are listed alphabetically by film title, followed by director name and production company, when possible.
    This subseries contains gay pornographic films in DVD format, covering a variety of sexual interests and themes.
    - 101 Loads. California, Pump House Media, 2006; cuid25143 (Box 31)
    - 1100 in Tuscon. Director Joe Gage. California, Titan Media, 2005; cuid25144 (Box 31)
    - 2 Twisted. California, Hot House Entertainment, 2005; cuid25145 (Box 31)
    - 2nd Gear. Director Chi Chi LaRue. California, Channel 1 Releasing, 2002; cuid25146 (Box 31)
    - Aggressive Bottoms from Hell. DW Media, 2004; cuid25147 (Box 31)
    - Anal Worshipers. B.A.L.L.S., 2003; cuid25148 (Box 31)
    - Ape Suit Three, 2002; cuid25149 (Box 31)
    - Ass Munching. B.A.L.L.S., 2003; cuid25150 (Box 31)
    - Back to Barstow. Director Joe Gage. California, Titan Media, 2004; cuid25151 (Box 31)
    - Below the Rim. Director Chi Chi LaRue. California, Channel 1 Releasing, 2003; cuid25152 (Box 31)
    - The Best of Buckshot. Various Directors. California, Colt Studio, 1999; cuid25153 (Box 31)
    - The Best of Colt Films: Parts 1, 2. Various Directors. California, Colt Studio, 2000; cuid25154 (Box 31)
    - The Best of Colt Films: Parts 3, 4. Various Directors. California, Colt Studio, 2000; cuid25155 (Box 31)
    - The Best of Colt Films: Parts 5, 6. Various Directors. California, Colt Studio, 2000; cuid25156 (Box 31)
    - The Best of Colt Films: Parts 7, 8. Various Directors. California, Colt Studio, 2001; cuid25157 (Box 31)
    - Betrayed. California, Falcon Studios, 1998; cuid25158 (Box 31)
    - Bisexual American Porn. Wisconsin, Digital Smut, 2005; cuid25159 (Box 31)
    - Brotherly Love. Metro Inc., 2002; cuid25160 (Box 31)
    - Buckshot Productions: Muscle Ranch. Various Directors. California, Colt Studio, 1999; cuid25162 (Box 31)
    - Buckshot Productions: Man To Man Heat. Various Directors. California, Colt Studio, 2001; cuid25161 (Box 31)
    - Buddy Booth. TPC Productions, Undated; cuid25163 (Box 31)
    - Butt Sluts at the Chateau Diablo. Jock in Socks (TNT Productions), 2002; cuid25164 (Box 31)
    - Chapters. Director David Wexler. California, Titan Media, 1997; cuid25165 (Box 31)
    - Channel 1 Releasing Collection vol. One. Director Chi Chi LaRue. California, Channel 1 Releasing, 2002; cuid25166 (Box 31)
    - Chop Suey. Director Bruce Weber, Undated; cuid25167 (Box 31)
    - Cocks on the Rocks. Dick Wado Media, 2005; cuid25168 (Box 31)
    - Colt: Wide Strokes. Director John Rutherford. California, Colt Studios, 2005; cuid25169 (Box 31)
    - Cum Catchers. California, LFP Video Group, 2006; cuid25170 (Box 31)
    - Cum Crazy Jiz Eaters. SX Video, Undated; cuid25171 (Box 31)
    - Cum Eater. SX Productions, 2004; cuid25172 (Box 31)
    - Cum Suckers 7: Overload. California, Factory Video Productions, 2003; cuid25173 (Box 31)
    - Cum Suckers 8: Mouthful. California, Factory Videos, 2004; cuid25174 (Box 31)
    - The Cum Suckers Trilogy. California, Factory Video Productions, 2001; cuid25175 (Box 31)
    - Cumsloppy Buttholes. Director Paul Morris. California, Treasure Island Media, 2004; cuid25176 (Box 31)
    - Damon Blows America 6. Director Paul Morris. California, Treasure Island Media, 2004; cuid25177 (Box 31)
    - Deep Inside. California, TNT Productions, 2002; cuid25178 (Box 31)
    - Deep Water. Beach Patrol: Part One. Director Joe Gage. California, Titan Media, 2006; cuid25179 (Box 31)
    - Demolitian Daddy. California, Big Blue Productions, 2000; cuid25180 (Box 31)
    - Desert Dungeon: Act 1-Act 6. (Gengoroh Tagame), Undated; cuid25181 (Box 31)
    - Desire. California, Titan Media, 2001; cuid25182 (Box 31)
    - Detention. Director Chi Chi LaRue. TLA Entertainment, 2003; cuid25183 (Box 31)
    - Detour. California, Titan Media, Undated; cuid25184 (Box 31)
    - Don't Ask Don't Tell. MSR Videos, 2000; cuid25185 (Box 31)
    - Dreamers. Director Kristen Bjorn. Florida, Kristen Bjorn Productions, 2002; cuid25186 (Box 31)
    - Drill to the Point. California, Titan Media, 2005; cuid25187 (Box 31)
    - Drunk on Cum 3. Director Paul Morris. California, Treasure Island Media, 2006; cuid25188 (Box 31)
    - Drunk on Cum 4. Director Paul Morris. California, Treasure Island Media, 2007; cuid25189 (Box 31)
    - Face Ryders. MSR Production, 2003; cuid25190 (Box 31)
    - Falcon Head Two: The Maneaters. California, LFP Video Group, 2003; cuid25191 (Box 31)
    - Fallen Angel III: Initiation. Director Bruce Cam. California, Titan Media, 1999; cuid25192 (Box 31)
    - Folsom Leather. California, Titan Media, 2007; cuid25193 (Box 31)
    - Gale Force: Men's Room II. Director Joe Gage. California, Titan Media, 2005; cuid25194 (Box 31)
    - Gay Ass Worship. California, Vidco Entertainment, 2001; cuid25195 (Box 31)
    - Gentle Gents. California, Metro Inc., 1999; cuid25196 (Box 31)
    - Glory Holes of Chicago. Director Bruno Riccelli. California, Oh Man Studios, 2000; cuid25197 (Box 31)
    - Gorge. Director Bruce Cam. California, Titan Media, 2002; cuid25198 (Box 31)
    - Handsome. California, Star Gaze Productions, 2000; cuid25199 (Box 31)
    - Heat. Director Bruce Cam. Titan Media, 2000; cuid25200 (Box 31)
    - Heavy Equipment. Star Gazed Production, 2000; cuid25201 (Box 31)
    - Hog Heaven. Dick Wado Media, Undated; cuid25202 (Box 31)
    - Holler. California, Titan Media, 2002; cuid25203 (Box 31)
    - Horse Fallen Angel 5. Director Bruce Cam. California, Titan Men, 2004; cuid25204 (Box 32)
    - Hot Times in Little Havana. Director Kristen Bjorn. Florida, Kristen Bjorn Productions, 1998; cuid25205 (Box 32)
    - Inside Paris. Director Michael Lucas. New York, Lucas Entertainment, 2002; cuid25206 (Box 32)
    - An Introductory Tour to the World of Titan Men. California, Titan Media, 2000; cuid25207 (Box 32)
    - The Isle of Men. Director Kristen Bjorn. Florida, Sarava Productions, 2001; cuid25208 (Box 32)
    - Jacked Up. California, Titan Men, 2000; cuid25209 (Box 32)
    - Jackhammered. Dick Wado Media, Undated; cuid25210 (Box 32)
    - 5 Joe Cage Classics. Director Joe Gage, Undated; cuid25211 (Box 32)
    - The Joint: A Penile Instituition. Director Jim Steel. California, Odyssey Group, Undated; cuid25212 (Box 32)
    - Jumpin' Jacks. Director Steven Scarborough. Hot House Entertainment Inc., 1996; cuid25213 (Box 32)
    - Kansas City Trucking Company. Dir Joe Gage, Undated; cuid25214 (Box 32)
    - Kick-Ass Porn. California, Raging Stallion Studios, 2006; cuid25215 (Box 32)
    - L.A. Sex Party. Director Tony Alizzi. California, MSR Videos, 2002; cuid25216 (Box 32)
    - Leather Ring Lunch. California, Gay Pride Pictures, 2001; cuid25217 (Box 32)
    - A Letter to True. Director Bruce Weber, Undated; cuid25218 (Box 32)
    - Like Honey. Director Paul Morris. California, Treasure Island Media, Undated; cuid25219 (Box 32)
    - Lost Exit. Director Billy Wyatt. California, Channel 1 Releasing, 2000; cuid25220 (Box 32)
    - Man Fever. California. Blue Men Productions, 2006; cuid25221 (Box 32)
    - Manifesto. Director Chris Ward. California, Raging Stallion Studios, 2005; cuid25222 (Box 32)
    - Manplay MP-005. California, Titan Media, 2002; cuid25223 (Box 32)
    - Manplay Xtreme. California, Titan Media, 2003; cuid25224 (Box 32)
    - Manplay Xtreme 2. California, Titan Media, 2003; cuid25225 (Box 32)
    - Massive Man Meat Frozen in Time... Catalina Videos, 2003; cuid25226 (Box 32)
    - Meat Packing. Director Paul Morris. California, Treasure Island Media, 2005; cuid25227 (Box 32)
    - Men's Room: Bakersfield Station. Director Joe Gage. California, Titan Media, 2004; cuid25228 (Box 32)
    - More Pigs at the Troff. Dick Wado Media, Undated; cuid25229 (Box 32)
    - Nexus Hardcore. Director Chris Ward. California, Raging Stallion Studios, 2002; cuid25230 (Box 32)
    - Nothin Nice. Director Steven Scarborough. California, Plain Wrapped Video, 1996; cuid25231 (Box 32)
    - Omega Centurion Muscle III. Director JD SLater. California, Raging Stallion Studios, 2006; cuid25232 (Box 32)
    - Orgy. Director Christopher Rage. California, Spunk Video, 2005; cuid25233 (Box 32)
    - The Other Side of Aspen I. California, Falcon Studios, 1995; cuid25234 (Box 32)
    - Pigs at the Zone. Dick Wado Media, 2006; cuid25235 (Box 32)
    - Piss Whores. California, SX Video, 2005; cuid25236 (Box 32)
    - Prowl 1, and Prowl 2. California, MSR Videos, 1998; cuid25237 (Box 32)
    - Prowl 5. Director Tony Alizzi. California, MSR Videos, 2005; cuid25238 (Box 32)
    - Ram Tough. California, Hot House Video, 2005; cuid25239 (Box 32)
    - R.E.M. California, Titan Media, 2002; cuid25240 (Box 32)
    - Revved Up. Director Matt Sterling. California, Atomic Video, 1999; cuid25241 (Box 32)
    - A Rim With A View. Director Hands Solo. California, Not Into Bush Productions, 2004; cuid25242 (Box 32)
    - Screw Right to the Point. California, Hot House Video, 2004; cuid25243 (Box 32)
    - Sea Men: Fallen Angel IV. Director Bruce Cam. California, Titan Media, 2001; cuid25244 (Box 32)
    - Service Trade. Directors Brian Mills and Harold Creg. California, Titan Media, 2003; cuid25245 (Box 32)
    - Sexpack Four: Porn Noir. Directors Chris Ward and J.D. Slater. California, Raging Stallion Studios, 2001; cuid25246 (Box 32)
    - Sexpack Reduxxx. California, Raging Stallion Studios, 2003; cuid25247 (Box 32)
    - Sex Pigs. California, MSR Videos, 2003; cuid25248 (Box 32)
    - Skuff 2: Downright Filthy. California, Hot House Entertainment, 2003; cuid25249 (Box 32)
    - Skuff 3: Downright Wrong. California, Hot House Entertainment, 2005; cuid25250 (Box 32)
    - Slammer. Directors Brian Mills and Harold Creg. California, Titan Media, 2002; cuid25251 (Box 32)
    - Sleaze. California, SX Video, 2004; cuid25252 (Box 32)
    - Slurpin' Jizz. Director Paul Morris. California, Treasure Island Media, 2004; cuid25253 (Box 32)
    - Slurpin' Jizz 2. Director Paul Morris. California, Treasure Island Media, 2005; cuid25254 (Box 32)
    - Steele Ranger. Director Chi Chi LaRue. California, Channel 1 Releasing, 1999; cuid25255 (Box 32)
    - Thick as Thieves. Director Kristen Bjorn. Florida, Kristen Bjorn Productions, 1998; cuid25256 (Box 32)
    - Tongue Devils. TNT Productions, 2002; cuid25257 (Box 32)
    - Total Corruption 1 and 2. Director Chi Chi LaRue. California, VCR Interactive, 1995; cuid25258 (Box 32)
    - Trespass. California, Titan Media, 2001; cuid25259 (Box 32)
    - What a Pisser! Oink Video, Undated; cuid25260 (Box 32)
    - White Trash. Director Tony Alizzi. California, MSR Videos, 2002; cuid25261 (Box 32)
    - You're So Fucking Nasty. TPC Productions, Undated; cuid25262 (Box 32)
- Series X. Clippings, 1997-2010, undated; cuid25264; 1 linear foot in 2 manuscript boxes. (Box 33, Folder 1-12, Box 34, Folder 1-9)
  This series contains images of men in fashion advertisements and on covers, removed from various fashion and lifestyle magazines including Details, GQ, Vogue, and Esquire. Clippings are taken from both US and foreign magazines. These clippings were very likely pulled by Marshall for book research.
  The materials were foldered and titles were written by a Fales student worker.
- Series XI. Dolls and Objects, 2003-2009, undated; 3.5 linear foot in one document box and 2 record cartons.; 1 sound disc (cd) 1 CD
  This series has been organized by an archivist, grouped in boxes according to an item's size.
  This series contains two Tom of Finland action figure dolls, one World War II Yugoslavian soldier action figure doll, a Tom of Finland Christmas ornament, a Japanese vibrator, and a signed Justin Bond music CD.
  - Tom of Finland collectible dolls (two) "001 Rebel" with accessories, 2003; cuid25267 (Box 35)
  - Tom of Finland Christmas ornament. Includes a Christmas card from the Tom of Finland Foundation, 2004; cuid25269 (Box 35)
  - "Hugo" (WWII Yugoslavian soldier, 1944) action figure in box with accessories, 2003; cuid25265 (Box 36)
  - Tank top t-shirt, from www.waterboys.com, in green camouflage pattern with "Pee all you can pee" printed in yellow lettering, undated; cuid25266 (Box 36)
  - Zipang anal vibrator. Made in Japan. (Unopened), undated; cuid25268 (Box 36)
  - Signed Justin Bond "Pink Slip" music CD, 2009; cuid25270 (Box 36)
  - "Carlos: The World's First-Out and Proud Boyfriend" doll figure in black leather, 1996; cuid25271 (Box 37)
- Series XII. Work Files, 1964-2008, undated; cuid25263; 1 linear foot in one record carton.; 1 electronic discs (cd-rom) (Box 38, Folder 1-19)
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist. Material was placed in acid free folders when necessary. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  Most of these files are related to the book Marshall was working on before his death: "Masters of Homoerotic Drawings." Files include a draft/mock-up of the book, containing images and title pages. This series also contains what was most likely research, including erotic magazines; exhibition catalogues, announcements, and invitations; images with a sexual theme; a CD-R disc of images, and correspondence.